Today, our live stream topic is the second lesson on the details of clothing.
Let's take a look at the content of our live stream first.
Let's see what we're going to do this time.
First of all, let's take a look at the first set.
The first set will be in a style like this.
The upper body is a...
The upper part is a bow tie.
And then the waist is a tie style.
And then take a look at the second set.
The second set...
You can take a look here.
It's mainly two parts.
The first part is the waistband.
There are two parts of the waistband.
One is the waistband.
How to tie it.
How to tie the waistband on the outer layer of the clothes.
The second one is how to do the details of this kind of dress.
This is the first part.
And then the second part is how to show the details of the rope on the hat.
Because everyone mentioned it before.
I want to do a horse rope.
Here.
Take a look.
There's a detailed picture of a horse rope.
Yeah.
How to show this kind of...
I'll talk about it later.
Let's get started.
Including everyone.
What else do you want to learn?
You can tell us in the chat.
And then we'll arrange it.
Okay.
Let's go to the Clou interface first.
First of all, let's open the first set.
Here, I'll open a virtual model first.
Is my voice okay now?
Okay.
Then let's import our paper sample.
Here, I'll choose the most common option.
Okay.
The board is in.
First of all, let's copy this board to the other side.
Copy it all out.
The waistband part, because I don't do it now.
So let's turn it back on first.
Okay.
Let's quickly arrange the volume for it.
Get closer to it.
What's next?
The front of this board is the part that needs to be twisted.
So we're in the process of sewing.
Don't sew all the sewing lines first.
I'll fix the necessary part for him first.
This is the collar and the back of the collar.
The place where the back collar is sewn.
And then I'll fix my side seam.
These two lines.
This part is going to be twisted later.
So don't sew it first.
It's not good to twist this knot when you sew it.
And my back.
Switch direction.
Okay.
In this way, I'm almost done with this part of the sewing line.
You can take a look.
Now I'm going to simulate it.
When we simulate it, we know that once we simulate it, the board will become soft.
Then I won't be able to control this shape later.
So before I simulate it, I'll use a fixing needle to fix my bottom first.
Okay.
This is the state for the time being.
Let's deal with the collar first.
I didn't finish sewing the back of the collar just now.
Because of the arrangement just now.
It's not suitable to sew it all at once.
Let's pull it a little bit here.
Okay.
Divide the back collar.
Let's make it into a curve.
Okay.
Simulate it.
Let's deal with the shape of this collar first.
Let's fold it again.
Because here we can see that its collar has a turning effect.
So let's make it a fold line here first.
And then you can use the edit curve tool here to make a curve.
Okay.
I will make the line a little bit curved
Then you can make the front part hard
Then you can set the angle of the line
Then my collar is ready
Next, I will deal with the knot
Take this needle off first
For the knot, we know that there will be a lot of wrinkles in the part of the knot
So if we have a large particle diameter, it is not easy to stabilize this part
In order to ensure that it is in a stable state during the process of the knot
We need to reduce the particle diameter of the two boards before we have them
Here is the particle diameter
You can reduce it here
You can reduce it to 10 or 8 according to the speed of your computer
To be more safe, you can reduce it to 10 first and then reduce it more
Then add a row of fixed needles to our lower salt
I will demonstrate the method of adding a row of fixed needles
Put your mouse on the outer salt line and find a blue dot
At this time, the double-click mouse left-click can quickly add a row of fixed needles
The other side is also
Then we can start to twist our
knot
At this time, I can move my board by pulling these fixed needles
At this time, you need to pay attention
Consider that there will be a lot of fabric accumulation in the front
At this time, the front and back sides of the board will overlap and stack together
This is to ensure stability
We can increase the conflict thickness of the two front pieces appropriately
In this way, it will ensure that there are more gaps on the outside of my board to prevent my board from bumping into each other
So increase the conflict thickness
I have increased it to 4
Then move
Then here is also
The advantage of adding a row of fixed needles is that we can use this positioning ball to rotate it
This is also
Then everyone has some little skills in the process of moving
The first one can see that when I pull my fixed needle, I will change my perspective from time to time
In order to find a more accurate position
The second one is that you are in the process of pulling
For example, I am now pulling to a state of collision
It is a key step
You can pause the simulation
In this way, the system can record the current state
If you accidentally pull the head and pull the board through
Then wait a minute, you can give it back to me
This step
Continue to pull
Pay attention when pulling
This place can be moved
Why
Our board is this point and this point later
So you need to turn it up
Move over
Then this side is also
You see
It's okay
Let's cancel it
You can cancel it back to the one that just paused the simulation
So stop it from time to time
There is another point here
Why did you pierce it just now
Because I pulled the fabric here too tight
So when everyone is doing it, be careful not to pull your fabric too tight
This will cause its grid to be particularly easy to penetrate
Turn it over
Turn it again
Good
This one goes here first
Continue to pause
Pull this out
To the left
At this time
This side also needs to be turned to him
Okay
In the pause
Continue
Stop it at the key step
Let's Doc
My
I
It is a little longer
Okay
This side and this side are close to each other because they are going to be sewn together later.
Okay, now it's almost here.
You can come over here a little bit more.
Okay, that's about it.
At this time, you can take my needle away.
Use the shortcut key here to delete all the fixed needles.
Okay, now I can put this side and this side just now.
Give it fixed together.
Because the other side is symmetrical, you don't have to sew it.
Let's simulate it.
This part is done.
Then we sew this opening part to it.
Note that there is a little trick here.
Don't sew it all at once.
Because this may bring some instability.
Let's sew a part of it first.
Leave a little, leave a little, simulate it.
Okay, at this time, we're going to put it in the middle.
Then consider it at this time.
We currently have a relatively large gap.
In other words, there will be a lot of gap in the middle.
It will occupy the space of this hole in the middle of me.
Then I'll sew it to the end.
It may cause me to have this gap.
The gap is too big.
The plates squeeze each other and cause instability.
So in this step.
The current step.
We need to reduce the gap.
Give it a little bit.
I reduced it to 3.
I don't dare to reduce it anymore.
Because it's already shaking.
So what should I do at this time?
Continue to reduce my particle holder.
It means that there are too many details in this place.
My particle holder is not enough to show me these details.
Still not enough.
I want to be a little safer.
I will reduce it to 5.
These two plates are reduced to 5.
My back is not moving.
The back is still 20 particle holders.
Okay.
Then, after my conflict, I will continue to reduce it to 2.
Of course, our final target is to reduce it to 1.
Now, we don't want to continue to reduce it for the time being.
Because we have to make a belt later.
So this side will be reduced to 1.
So this side is currently stopped at 2.
And then we didn't die here just now.
Now put it.
Use the
So soon, the part of this twist is already finished.
What skills did you say just now?
Which step are you referring to?
Can you ask more details?
Summarize.
The core points of this twist.
One is that the particle holder of the twist plate must be reduced.
The impact thickness must be increased.
The second point is that in the process of pulling the plate with a fixed needle,
Stop the simulation from time to time.
To record the current correct state.
In fact, this is a little skill point.
You can practice it according to this at that time.
Now we have completed this twist.
Let's make a freeze.
Next, let's deal with the belt part.
The belt, you can take a look at this effect.
We are like a simulation.
The real way to make this twist belt.
There are usually two ways to make a twist in 3D.
One is to make a fake one in the form of powder.
The other one is like what we are going to talk about now.
It's a real way to make a twist.
Let's activate these two belts.
Now, in order to make it easier for me to operate,
I need to make a simple arrangement for this plate.
Click on the plate.
There is a small mark on the upper right corner of the positioning ball.
It is a tool for smart arrangement of plates.
Press the mouse button on the model.
You can quickly arrange it.
Just put it in a general way.
The position does not need to be very precise.
Approximately close.
Here too.
Close.
OK .
Just about.
At this time, I sew my belt to it.
Sew my side seam in the back.
Because the belt panel plate is not symmetrical,
so sew both sides.
Next.
You can put the front part of this part using the fixed needle.
Fix it
If you make a knot, the first knot we will just go around
Then go around in 3D
It's going to be very difficult to make another knot
So let's simplify it a little bit
The first part of the knot is sewed in the way of the inner line
To fix it
So here we use the inner line tool
Draw one for it
Ctrl-C, Ctrl-V
Copy to the other side
Then separate these two
Simulate
Get closer
Why get closer
It depends on whether the position you sewed is appropriate
We hope this is the fixed position
We normally tie the fixed position
It's tight but not too tight
What do you mean
If you use a pressure map to check
Should not be too good
It's too red
Also check your pressure map
Take a look at this color
OK
If the pressure map appears red
This board has stretched too much
Excessively stretched
So it's ok now
So I'll keep it here
Is such a position
it is good
What's next
I can take this fixed needle
Take it off
Because I didn't pause the simulation just now
So there is a little problem
it is good
Now I can take my fixed needle
Next
I'm going to do the same
The second knot
Because the first knot is fixed with a sewing line
So the second knot
To start doing
Let's take a look at this picture
There are a lot of wrinkle details on it
Just like the idea
Before knotting
First reduce the particle diameter
Otherwise
I can't hit this knot steadily
How much to reduce first
Reduce to 8 first
Wait a minute
Reduce gradually
Let's go to 8 for now
Because 8 can ensure that your speed is still relatively smooth
In the same way
In the process of knotting
In order to prevent it from colliding
We can put this
The thickness of the collision is also appropriately increased for it
For example, let me go to 3 first
it is good
What's next
Just like the idea
I can add a row of fixed needles to it at this edge
it is good
Let's simulate
Next we are going to knot
When knotting
Pay attention
Don't pull this rope too tight
In a loose state
The same is to pause the simulation from time to time
Remember the current state
What about knotting
First of all
We know that knotting needs a hole
Let your board come out of this hole
Make a knot
So first
Let's add a point on the board first
A fixed needle
Add another fixed needle
I added two here
One two
Make a hole shape
Then on the other board
It is also pressed
W single left button
You can quickly add needles
I am now choosing the move tool
Keep this needle
Now there is a hole shape
Then this
You can lower its position
Pause simulation at this time
Let's continue
Put this board
Turn it around here
Turn it around
At this time
In fact, this board
These needles are no longer needed
Because I can come over
Next
Find a way to put me here
Part of the hole
Out of the hole
So here
You may need to find a point
For example
I am here
Hold a point
Start simulation
The same
You need to go
Keep switching your perspective
You see I have been turning the perspective
Keep turning your perspective
To find a suitable position
To see your needle in the hole
Then pull this needle up with this basket
You can put this knot through
At this time
To prevent this knot
Straight out of the hole
Let's add a fixed needle to it below
Press W single left button
Okay
Now I can take this needle
Take it off
Take this needle
And there's another needle in it
Here
Take it off
This is over
Pause
Pause simulation
You can also take this needle
Simplify
Now
There's the shape of this knot
We will next
Slowly tighten this knot for it
Add a fixed needle below
Pull it down
At this time, this knot will slowly become tighter and tighter
That's the same
In this position
Let's take a look at this position and put it in
So let's analyze it here
This side is connected to the tail
The link is the end of my belt
So I need to put my fixed needle
Add it inside
Ah, take this needle out of here
Then lift this fixed needle up
In the process of you bringing it up
In fact, I have been tightening this knot slowly
Hey, I seem to have brought it back
It's okay
Let's bring it up again
Bring it up
Ah, it's stopped at this time
You can see it's sliding up slowly
But it's already shaking and unstable
This is to ensure your details
Just to finish this detail steadily
Ah
We need to continue to reduce the particle diameter
Ah, from 8 down to 5
it is good
The conflict thickness must be reduced
Because there are too many gaps in the middle
Your knot is always solid
So put this
Conflict thickness down to 2
Simulate
Don't go down to 2 first
Because we haven't finished this knot yet
Ah, at this time, you will find that the back is too straight
What to do if it's fake
Ah, you can put this inner line
Hey, let him line up first
I didn't see it in front of me
Ah, these two inner lines
You can actually choose one
Because the two of them are
Ah, they are together
Choose one of them and tighten the elasticity
Tighten it to 80 to 40
Tighten it a little bit
Of course, you can continue to receive 20
All right
But 20, it won't be stable
Because it's too much fabric accumulation
Let's tighten it at the end
For the time being, 40 is guaranteed to be stable
Ah
Now it's 40
Now it's like this
Let's continue to go up
Tighten this knot
Ah
Pause the simulation
You can be here
Consider adding a needle to it
At the top
Point position
What else do you have to consider
This knot can't be too far from my body
Otherwise, I won't force the needle
So you can put this needle close to the model's body
Next is to put this needle close to the model's body
It will not be flowing Well
Then, the knot will be close to the model's body
Ah
Continue to continue pulling
At this time, continue to pull
It may need to give it more space
So
Ah
What about this time
There is a way
Because now this particle interval is 5
If we continue to 3
Can take a look
She will be more stable
But it's hard to tighten it again
Because the conflict of 1 is more dangerous
So at this time
You can use a function to look at the shrinkage first.
I want to check the direction of the gold sand on this board.
I hope my board is in the direction of the gold sand, which is the horizontal direction, so that it becomes longer.
Imagine that after the board becomes longer, it will have more space.
I can pull it tighter.
So now I'm going to make its golden shrinkage to 110.
I'm going to make it 120 again, and I'm going to simulate it.
Okay, now it's loose.
Continue to use my fixed needle to tighten it.
You can take this needle away.
There's another needle in here.
Pull this needle up.
And then I'm going to connect this one.
Pull it down.
You can tighten this knot slowly.
Of course, here, too.
Here's one.
I'm afraid to pull it down.
You need to wait a while.
Let this board tighten slowly.
It's tightened by sliding.
I'm already at 3 now.
It's a little dangerous at this time.
Maybe if your computer doesn't give you the right configuration, it might get stuck.
Okay, slow down.
Now, for example, I think this knot is almost there.
I'm going to make sure my fixed needle is tightened.
And then we're going to slowly restore this shrinkage.
You have to be a little slower at this time.
It's going to get tighter.
At this time, I'm going to pull this knot through the shrinkage.
Restore to 100.
It's going to be tighter.
If you think this knot is almost there.
What about now?
Continue to reduce this elasticity.
Because you want it to be tighter.
behind
Then now I have this knot effect.
For example, I don't think I need to adjust it anymore.
In order to prevent it from being unstable later.
You can use a fixed needle to fix this knot.
Then we're going to adjust the top and bottom shapes.
For example, I'm going to find an area of a knot.
That's half of it.
There's another half here.
I didn't find it.
Add it again.
Okay, I didn't find this position.
It doesn't matter.
I'm going to adjust it.
Continue to find a little bit down.
Can you make a big friction?
Yes, of course.
But there's a little bit of friction.
It's still going to have a chance.
Slowly loosen this knot.
So if you want to make sure.
Maintain the current state.
The best thing is to add a fixed needle.
Because the fixed needle.
He can fix this position to him.
Fix it.
A little bit.
Press the control key.
You can cut off a part of the needle.
Cut a little bit more.
Almost this position.
And then here, too.
Give him a fix.
Press the control plus shift.
You can choose this needle more.
Because I didn't choose the right position just now.
Choose a little more.
Someone just said the friction coefficient.
If you want to adjust the friction coefficient.
Select this branch.
At the bottom of the attribute converter.
Open your branch.
The details of the attribute setting.
Find the number of friction.
If it's three.
You can adjust it to forty or fifty.
Then he can.
It's not as easy to slide as it used to be.
But he's still a little bit of a slide.
So why didn't I set this here?
The number of friction.
One is because I just said.
He's not that fixed.
The other one.
It's because I'm going to have to adjust it later.
My upper ear.
There are two tails at the bottom.
So if I'm going to make the friction coefficient bigger now.
It's not very convenient to adjust later.
It's not very convenient.
So I didn't use the friction coefficient here.
Just because I'm here.
I made a.
Tighten it.
So you can pull this way.
Let him re-model it.
So he might have more frictions.
There's one more thing.
What we're doing now.
This fabric.
You can apply it to him.
Because the fabric will affect the shape of this part.
And the shape of our ears and tails.
So here.
I'll give him one first.
Silk-type fabric.
For example, this piece of fabric.
Choose my two plates.
I'll use it.
Re-model it.
Now let's adjust the details.
The details.
If.
How do you do it?
I'll teach you today.
The last part of today's lesson is to teach the original god.
Sometimes it's easy to take it off when you pull it hard.
So I just talked about pulling the plate.
Be careful not to let it stretch too much.
If you stretch it too much.
The net will crack.
So you see me when I was pulling.
I was very careful.
Just a little bit of pressure on him.
Let him slowly slide by himself.
Just didn't give him.
Add an unreasonable force.
Let's take this.
Let's adjust the shape above.
What about the shape here?
You can consider this.
Take off the fixer.
Let him simulate it naturally.
When you simulate it.
You turn it down a little bit.
I see this place.
It's already causing me this.
It doesn't look very natural, does it?
Find this position.
Cut it off a little bit.
That means you've chosen too much.
Find this position.
Is it here?
No, it's not here.
Let's take a look at the upper part.
Find this position.
It's not here either.
It doesn't matter.
You can frame it here.
See where it appears.
Near this.
Take this area off a little bit.
Let him naturally hammer down.
In the process of natural hammering down.
You can pull it a little bit.
Let him adjust it a little bit better.
Add a fixer.
Adjust it a little bit better.
That's the same thing down there.
You have to pull it a little bit lighter when you pull it.
Pull it slowly.
If you pull it too hard all of a sudden.
It will cause that.
This string has been floating around.
It will take a lot of time to adjust it to stabilize it.
So pull it a little bit slower.
Wow, old fans.
Who?
It's too good.
Pull it out a little bit.
Pull it out a little bit on this side.
Just pull this tail out.
It'll look better.
Okay, pause.
You don't have to completely ban it.
You can just adjust it to the point where you think it looks better.
Come a little bit over here.
It's too much.
Of course, if you think this one.
The belt is too wide.
You can.
Through the way of pulling.
Of course, you can help with the pin.
Let him have a little bit of folding effect.
Okay, pause.
Basically, I think I'm almost here.
It's almost what I want.
And then this needle.
You can just keep it here.
Don't take it off.
Why?
Because this needle can be hidden.
It doesn't really matter after it's hidden.
And then this is the belt plate.
Usually, there will be multiple layers.
Or two layers.
So here.
You can properly make it thicker.
A little thicker.
Then his details look a little more realistic.
In this case, I'm basically done with this style.
Now I can activate this.
Activate the back of it.
Finally, improve the quality.
One is the surface diameter of the model to zero.
I'll show you.
The second one is my plate.
The two pieces behind me.
It's going to be a particle diameter of five.
Interference thickness to one, right?
The previous two pieces of particle diameter have reached five.
But the interruption thickness is a little slower.
Let him simulate it like this first.
After stability.
I'm going to put the previous two pieces of particle diameter to one.
Let me see if he can stabilize it.
Make sure it's stable.
If it's not stable.
Just a little bit.
It's two to one point five.
One point five to one like this.
It's okay.
It's more stable.
In the end.
You can delete my fold line.
Because it's not very natural to leave a line.
Delete the fold line.
You can hide one of them.
To observe the shape of this hole.
It's round.
It means it's stable.
If there's something in the middle of it.
突起
For example, there are some sharp triangles here.
That means he's fighting slowly.
You have to be careful at this time.
In this case, we'll finish this style.
At this time, this style.
If you want to change your posture.
For example, I'm from.
The open to the straight.
This is OK.
No problem.
But suppose you have a lot of action.
At this time, you have to be careful.
You have to take off the fixing needle.
What do you do after you take it off?
You can use a fake needle.
To put it in an important position.
Set it up.
To prevent your board from sliding.
The same.
At this time, add that bigger friction.
The number.
Increase its friction.
And then change the posture.
It's okay.
You can do it.
What is the surface of the model?
Click model.
You can see the model surface of the model on the mouse.
The model surface of the model refers to the model surface.
It will have an air thickness to prevent my board from touching my model.
This is to prevent some conflicts between the board and the model.
It's actually with the board.
The thickness of the conflict is very similar to a setting.
The thickness of the conflict of the board is on the surface of the board.
There is such an air thickness to prevent the board from touching each other.
I haven't applied the fabric to it yet.
Apply a fabric to the sound.
When I was doing the style before, you can see that I didn't put on the fabric at the beginning.
Because of the fabric of this kind of silk.
It has a characteristic.
It's going to be very light.
It's going to be very floaty.
When you twist it like this.
It's hard.
I'm going to control it.
So I suggest that when you're doing this kind of detail, you can do it with the default fabric first.
After you're done, give it to him.
Switch to the real plant.
So this style is done.
We can put this one.
In the end, for example, I change a silk satin material.
You can change it to a color, etc.
You can complete this style.
I'll save it.
We started.
This knot and knot belt is done.
Let's do the next one.
How can I say the next knot again?
Today's time is limited.
You can wait for the recording to come out later.
Take a look at it again.
Look at what everyone said in the chat.
What did you say?
Like this.
Recording tomorrow can't go up.
It's going to take a week.
We're talking about the next style.
If you want to go home early today, you might be off school today.
And then let's look at the second set.
The second set will show you the content.
It's probably something like this.
But we're not going to start from the beginning today
Because of time
We take the most important, the most core
The details that everyone pays attention to
Take it out and talk about it
So first of all, I'm going to open a semi-finished product
How to add a whole row of fixed needles
Let me show you again
Look at the screen
Use the fixed needle tool to find the outline of the plate
You can see that there are a lot of grid on it
Put your mouse on any of them
On any top point
When you see the blue dot, double-click the left mouse button
You can complete the addition of a row of fixed needles
Let's start talking about the second part
How to display it again after the color is hidden
Single-click 3D tablet
There is a hidden 3D tablet on the right
See the express key
Shift Q is to hide it
If it is in the selected state
You shift Q again and it will show
But suppose you have hidden multiple tablets
At this time, on the background
Right click
Right click on the background
There is no here
Here
Put your mouse on the left corner of the scroll menu
See there is a display 3D clothing
The first one
Display clothing
Shift W
That is to say
Suppose you have hidden multiple tablets
Just press Shift W
You can display it all
OK
Let's go down
Come on
Select my
If I am now in the 2D selection of the tablet
It is selected in a group
Because I put all the large tablets together
It uses a new function of our 5.2
That is, when you select multiple tablets and right-click
There is a group function
Now I want to
First of all
The first one is the belt part
But in order to take the belt
We know that this style is a loose style now
I can't take my belt
Give it to him
Just fit on the outside of a loose style
Because at that time I went
Even if the layer is set
It is also difficult to let all the
All the loudness is thrown into my belt
So to make it more convenient
Come and wear my belt
We can put the sound first
The tablet is tightened
Make it a close-up
Then I can't change the paper
At this time, use
One of our functions is called shrink
I've used it just now
Select my sound tablet
Find the final shrink in the mouse machine
The final shape is not certain
You can use the edit text tool
Check it
Look at the mirror
The final shape is to reduce the final shrink
The final shrink is adjusted to 90
Then turn off the simulation at 80
Simulation
Turn off the simulation at 70
Here I suggest that everyone can come a little bit
So you can ensure that your clothes are stable
Otherwise, if you change too much at once
May cause the clothes to be a little unstable
Unstable situation
That is to say, you step by step
If you increase the shrinkage, it will be more stable
I just pulled the clothes up a little bit
why
I want my whole waistline to go up a little bit
it is good
Now I have become a
Comprehensive style
Then I'm going to do the belt
When I do the belt
I just consider my sound
All other versions actually don't need simulation
So at this time
Select all versions
Control A full selection
There is a freeze on the right arrow on the board
You can do it in 2D
You can do it in 3D right arrow
You can do it here
There is a freeze
Next, do the belt
Do the belt
First of all, if we normally do one
For example, it is a couple
How to do if you make a long belt knot
We have already talked about the knot just now
Now let's talk about how to do the belt
Suppose
Suppose I have a very long plate here
For example, the height is 50
I just drew a plate like this
The tool used is this plate tool
Long plate tool
May not be long enough
I will continue to make it a little longer
Then we put this plate
Arranged on my body
Apply a default object
Just like the default object
Will be faster
Then you can see this plate
Folded, right?
In the property editor
Find one of our bars
Select this plate
After arranging
It will appear such an option
Use this bar to open your plate
Of course, don't open it too much
It's not good if it overlaps with the costume
Come back a little more
Y-axis can go up a little
it is good
At this time
Put it to the side
Move it forward a little
Now find a point
Find this point
Find my belly
This belly is a little forward
Can guarantee me later
When I sew the fixed belt
Will not penetrate my model
Found
I clicked
The blue dot will appear in the 2D version
Single machine, double machine
I use this internal line tool
it is good
Also draw one here
Then
Give him my belt
So I will give him the belt
Fixed
This state is familiar
Just now we are doing the first set
Take a look
The waist part of the first set
Is it also
First sew two plates
Fix it
Then you can tie it
So here
I won't repeat it
Just teach everyone how to tie here
This is the first kind of knot
What about the second kind
Let's do it
The style is our suit
This belt on the clothes
Here
How to do this belt
First of all
I still use this
Long-sleeved plate tool
Draw a belt
Width
About 680
It's almost the same as my waist
But a little wider
Because we are going to put clothes in it later
So leave a little gap
Width
The height is the width of my belt
Just 8 cm wide
it is good
This belt
Still arrange it for him
Arrange it
it is good
Next
This belt
You can sew it up
But pay attention to our belt
There is a gap in the middle
This gap is going to be left
Let me wear it
So here
When fixing the belt
Can be used
Fitting tool to fix
Instead of using a sewing tool
Fitting tool
Press
In my other point
Position
Press again
You can complete a pair
The seam line
What kind of graphics card is the computer?
My graphics card is 2070
Max
2070 Super
That graphics card
Down
Copy a few for him
Copy a few more
Fitting line
Confirm
it is good
Then this way
After the seam line is done
If I simulate it now
You can take a look
It's completely stuck
So before we simulate
We need to put this seam line
Set the length of the line
Just let him keep a certain gap in the middle
Here, for example
I set a 1 cm gap
Then before the simulation
Take a look
The board just now is very soft
Then we have to make a leather here
So I'm using a leather plant here
That leather plant
What is the attribute of the leather plant?
Let me tell you
Take a look
In the physical attribute details
See its gold tail sand strength
I set it very high
Because basically the belt is not much
Can stretch
Then its bending strength is 90
Very high
First of all, its gold image
Gold image
See its gold image
It can't bend
So the gold image must be very high
Then its tail
It should have a certain bending
So the tail
If you want to be reasonable
You can set it to 70
You can also lower the sand a little bit
But in fact, there is not much difference here
If you really simulate it
There is not much difference
In short, the core of this belt
Is to be a little harder
I feel this belt
A little bit
See if he is a little bit down
We are not now
Can't tighten this belt
Because we have to keep some space
In order to prevent
Wait for our clothes to shrink
Still have to return
Then leave him a little bit
To give him enough space
How to make my belt
Can be straighter
It looks good
Stay here
Can use
Our conflict thickness
Make the conflict thickness larger
This can ensure
Your board
There is an air thickness outside
Then your belt
It feels like something is wrapped inside
It will be more
A little more
Of course you can
A little bigger
A little more
it is good
Good
Let him
This place is also
Don't go up
Take a look
Maybe too much
It's 10
Don't be too much
In this state
The position of my belt is almost
Next do my
hole
Because I want to wear it
First of all, there is a hole
Use our inner circle
Then add the inner circle
When
You can directly
Single left-click inside the board
That's fine
What about this inner circle
I made it 10 mm wide
Then its number
I'm going to do four
You can see that the angle is not quite right
So turn it
You can try
0 degrees up
It should be 180 degrees down
Make him a little bigger
Then what do you set him
I'd better set him
A precise value
Why
Wait a minute
Add that circle
If I set the position
It will be more convenient to add a circle
So here
Located in the center
For example, it is 10 mm above the top
Then 10 mm to the left
Click to confirm
OK
Select the inner circle in the center
Transform into a hole
Then ctrl c ctrl v
Copy it to the other side
In the process of copying
I press the shift key
To keep it level
At this time
Don't press the left key
Because
I want to make its position
It's relative to the other side
That is to say the same position
At this time
Press the shift key
Don't press the right button
At this time
You can pop out a window
To these inner circles
Make a positioning
The positioning here
You can see this center point
The center point is right
Should be
It corresponds to my left
Click to confirm
So my
The hole is ready
Now see this circle
Not very smooth
Because we are now
The particle diameter is too large
Then wait to wear the rope
In order to ensure that you wear the rope
The process is stable
Your belt
The particle diameter
Also has to be reduced a little
First to 8
Of course
You can also consider
Lower to 5
It's ok
To 5
Ok
Then the belt
Its thickness
It should be thicker
Is its
We will make it thicker
A little thicker
Look at this
Make it thicker
Make it 2mm
The thickness of the
This belt is already done
I'll give it
Freeze
You can freeze it here
I use the shortcut key
Control key
The belt is complete
Next, wear the rope
Before wearing the rope
Confirm one thing
My belt surface
You can return it to 2
Or
Confirm 2.5
You can also go to 2.5
I'll go to 2
Then
Let's do this
Wear the rope
There is a little trick for the rope
If you want to wear a wide rope
In the process of wearing
Make it a little narrower
Make a thin rope first
Don't make a wide rope
So here
My hole is
10mm wide
My side
I'll do 5mm first
Wait a minute
Then slowly adjust it
Thicker
Adjust wide
If you want to adjust the height
Give it a 100
Of course, you can also adjust it a little longer
For example, 150
A little longer
The same
I want to get it close to here
So use the location ball
Put this icon in the upper right corner
Put it over
Ready to wear
What to pay attention to before wearing
One
Before wearing
The chest of drawers of my board
Can't be too big
Otherwise I can't wear it
So the small one
The small one
Directly to 3
Wait a minute
Let's see if it's suitable when wearing
What else is the problem
In the process of wearing
You can see
The gap between these two boards
Very small
So it will cause me
The difficulty of moving
Increase
For more convenient wear
We can put it first
This board
Do it to him
Reactive fire board
Let it disappear
Hiding
Shift Q
The model also makes it disappear
Right click
Right click on the model
Reactive fire model
Ok
Shift Q again
Shift A
Hide the model
Here
Show the model
Shift A
Hide it
Ok
Next, prepare to wear
If you wear it
I am above
That can be considered
Use the fixer
Add a row
Don't be too much
Just a row
Also for convenience
Wait a minute
Control my direction
Ok
Fix the needle
Show out
Now this default
Is leather
Is our last
Added
This leather is too hard
So
Apply a default
Then start wearing
Use the position ball
Push in
Come
At this time
You can put your
Turn it
Turn your board
Don't let him twist
It's best to let him wear it evenly
So you can handle it better
If he twists too hard
Then you can
You can turn it
Turn it
If it's too hard
A if it's看
Good
Not Quantum
comentarios
Another one
He will lead him to be more easy
It is in
Wait
I have two layers
This early
At the base
It's easy to puncture
So
Make sure your Whoa
The rope is flat
Another
Another point is what
Put up
诶,没出来,再过来,再进去啊,看一下下面,看这个地方快不够了啊,赶紧暂停一下,把下面呢,延长一点啊,再继续。
这里遇到了一点问题,重新加一下针。
好,进去,再出来。
差不多到中间就可以了。
因为等一下我们还有另外一半要做啊。
好,另外一半呢,不需要再重新穿一遍了。
直接Ctrl-C,Ctrl-R,Ctrl-R是什么呢?
板屏上右键可以看到有一个镜像粘贴,叫Ctrl-R。
可能有人会说能不能做对称的,Ctrl-D啊,也可以。
也可以,比如说做个Ctrl-D。
到正前方,按一下2,到正前方,用定位球的红轴啊,把它水平向左移动。
这样就正好能让它从这些洞里穿出来。
然后Ctrl-W是删除了所有固定针。
把上沿线,因为是对称的,所以我只要选一边,给它合并。
这个位置合并就可以了。
合并之后呢,这边给它做短一点。
因为是上下对称,就是它两边是对称的,只要调一边就可以了。
调完之后呢,把这个上下给它缝起来。
为什么呢?我们等于是把一个绳子拆分成两部分啊。
一个部分是穿的,做完我就可以对它进行一个冷冻。
把它这个往下拉一点。
好,冷冻住了。
可以慢点冷冻啊。
因为我们那个刚刚说到,如果你要做宽绳怎么办?
假设你现在穿完了,然后呢,如果你是个宽绳,你就现在可以把它去调宽。
按住左键拖动,左键不放单击右键,可以弹出这个窗口。
那这个宽度是多少?我刚刚是5。
先慢慢的一点点调宽啊,到6。
已经不太稳定,有点抖动了。
所以这时候把粒子进去降到1。
这个穿绳的细节还是要把粒子进去做低啊。保证它稳定。
继续。
6,比如说我现在直接给它到8。
模拟一下。
如果说你跨越多个竖直,不稳定,那就撤回来一个一个竖直的加啊。
好,差不多了。
然后这个绳子呢,应该是有厚度的,所以渲染的厚度给它加厚到1啊。
好。
看似好像完成了,对不对?
等一下,我们看一下这个细节啊。
等一下是要做扭扣的,可以看到。
那为了让我的绳子正好看着像从就是洞里面穿出来,不和扭扣交叠的话,我们有一个设定啊。
把腰带的冲突厚度做大。
那这样的话可以让你的板片更加远离这个洞,就是正好从洞中间穿出来。
等于是给扭扣留了一个空隙啊。
所以这也是一个小细节。
好。
好,把它冷冻住。
接下来来做它的尾巴。
刚刚说到它的宽度是8啊。
就是我这儿把它做成高度8毫米。
宽度的话就是我做长一点。
200,心脏是200。
等一下都可以调啊。
好。
好像不够长了。
我们再给它调长一点。
再长一点。
好,差不多这样。
好。
然后呢,给它做内部线间距。
给它做两个内部线。
干什么用呢?
等一下就知道了。
给它做两根吧。
80。
两个内部线啊。
然后同样的用这个快速安排的,安排过来。
换过来。
好。
用这个翻折工具。
先翻过来一下。
再翻回去一下。
为什么要这么做呢?
为了做一个耳朵和一个尾巴。
好。
加一个固定针。
等一下我要模拟了。
看到我这个板片为了稳定啊。
同样粒子间距。
因为这个板片太小了。
粒子间距到3。
加两个固定针。
然后给它缝一下。
那缝的时候呢,把我的起始端和我跳开一个内部线到第二个内部线啊。
也就是这两个分起来。
然后再把这个和谁。
和中间的这个翻一下。
模拟一下。
为什么要加固定针?
等一下就知道了啊。
好。
这边也是。
你可以直接对称Ctrl D啊。
我这边先不对称。
Ctrl C, Ctrl R就是镜像粘贴。
为什么?
等一下我想做两个不一样长的尾巴。
所以就不要给它做一个对称了。
然后呢。
我们把这个和这个里面的这个短的分一下。
你可以把它拉出来一点。
检查一下你的缝线有没有反啊。
这边是没有反的。
好。
然后我这边呢。
想要给它再更加逼真一点做一个截头。
因为我们打截是有个截头的。
好。
我这边呢。
可以把这个激活啊。
把这两个板片的冲突弧度做低一点到1吧。
让它扁一点啊。
但是它们的厚度要出来。
渲染厚度到1。
模拟一下。
好。
现在这个地方空隙太小了。
不好。
就不方便我等一下去做一个截头。
因为我要塞个截头进去啊。
所以这里呢。
可以考虑用你的手开启模拟盘往下拉。
暂停模拟。
那这样等于是人为的拉出了一个空隙。
给它冷冻住。
接下来做它的截头。
做个这个截头宽度呢。
假设比如说8毫米。
高度的话。
我先随便画一个啊。
因为这个等下都是可以调的。
所以没有关系。
然后呢。
给它做两个内部线。
干什么用呢。
用来把它翻折一下。
好。
找一下我的小板片。
然后用我们的翻折工具。
看了眼你们的弹幕。
说有学到新的技能。
那说明今天来对了。
这个小板片的粒子线就给它降低啊。
因为它非常的小。
然后在这个位置很危险。
所以直接降低到1。
然后呢。
把这个上下模拟。
那个缝纫一下。
好。
模拟。
你看它正好把它套住就可以了。
然后这两个内部线就可以删掉了。
好。
然后这个板片呢。
你可以慢慢的通过调它的长度把它收紧。
然后我这边用了一个功能。
可能太快了。
选出两个边。
在这里右键有个线段兼创建内部线。
那默认直接是一个中心线啊。
然后把它给切断。
切断做什么呢。
你可以做一个比如说把上下。
上下。
上下给它合并。
因为这一个结有点太生硬了。
就直接这样一个结套在上面可能有点太生硬啊。
所以你可以直接上下缝一下。
这样让它这个结有一个错落。
好。
然后同样的再把它收紧一点。
冲突厚度呢。
可以考虑降低一点。
渲染厚度增大。
好。
等冻住。
这个结就可以了。
然后呢我们把这个。
两个带子激活。
把固定针拿掉。
我按了ctrl w。
把固定针给它删除掉了。
把它放下来。
弄一下啊。
然后这两根带子上的这个。
零度的翻折线删掉。
拉一下。
防止它的惯性过大。
好。
这样这根带子就完成了。
接下来呢我们模特可以给它激活了。
激活虚拟模特。
然后也是激活我的服装啊。
这个地方你这时候你可以看到它的带子进去了啊。
没有关系。
为了保证你等一下是稳定的。
你可以使用这个。
选择网格工具去爬拉。
选择网格工具去爬拉出来。
大概是哪个部分。
一个是带子的部分。
还有是我中间的这个部分。
转一下。
让它出来。
如果你想要调长度等一下再调。
我们先把这个大声给它还原回来啊。
把大声激活。
嗯。
全部都激活吧。
全部。
Ctrl A全选。
然后除了你的这些部分啊。
其他的都激活。
然后呢你把这个大声部分的那个那个缩率一点点给它放出来啊。
一点一点放。
40到50。
这时候千万不能急。
急了的话你可能就前功尽弃了啊。
你一定要慢一点。
50到60模拟一下。
还可以啊。
你要转着去检查。
然后70。
再模拟一下。
转一下。
检查一下。
然后再到80。
再模拟一下。
这时候可以看到褶皱越来越多了。
那这时候是有点危险。
所以在这时候大声的力量就会适当的降低啊。
比如说到10。
是为了让它更加稳定的去表现出它腰部的细节。
好。
80到90再模拟一下。
然后90到100再模拟一下。
这样子的话就把你的衣服还原出来了。
那其实这个刚刚做的这个结啊。
就是我前面讲的第二种假的做结的方式啊。
这里要慢一点。
因为你的。
你看到刚才我在做这个还原的时候。
我没有把我的。
就是绳子给冷冻着。
为什么?
因为可以看到当我把衣服还原出来之后。
这个地方是会鼓出来的。
如果说你不让你的绳子去模拟的话。
是没有足够的空隙让你这个衣服出来。
可能会导致不稳定。
所以干脆就让你的这个绳子飘动着。
跟你的大声一起模拟。
一起放出来。
好。
然后这里的话可以稍微扯一下。
因为我们刚刚在那个。
用速率的时候。
它把那个袖口都往里缩了。
所以为了让它更加自然呢。
你可以稍微扯动一下。
当然不要扯太厉害。
然后呢。
来。
选中大声。
冷冻住。
为了为的是。
提高你的模拟速度。
因为刚刚说我希望做两个不一样长度的尾巴。
所以现在选中我下面的这一个线啊。
我没有用。
编辑。
调整版片。
因为如果用调整版片呢。
你的这个内部线的位置会发生偏移。
那这个地方你细节能做好。
如果一旦内部线偏移了。
这个地方就会不稳定。
所以使用是编辑版片。
只移动。
这个线段。
而不是调整整个版片的比例啊。
这边也调大。
可以看到这边出来了。
没有关系。
选择网格。
选中它。
让它转出来。
模拟一下。
好。
然后比如说再错落再明显一点。
那这样子的话。
这个腰带。
跟这个穿绳的结都完成了。
嗯。
其实最后的话也比较简单啊。
跟刚刚做的。
刚刚做的还有一点差距。
对吧。
刚刚这边还是有扭扣的。
所以呢。
现在呢。
我就把这个相对应的绳带。
来应用这个。
嗯。
就是红色的这根织带的。
面料啊。
其实这里模不模拟无所谓。
就是其实因为绳子的。
它的物理属性的差异的体现。
其实是非常微弱的。
就是这么一小块地方。
没有必要再模拟它。
因为你可能。
因为这种拉伸性的差异。
会模拟出不稳定的情况。
所以这里可以不用模拟。
好。
这里直接给它做扭扣。
那扭扣这个细节。
其实在上一次。
就是我们那个细节制作上。
就是上一次直播的时候。
我们IV老师其实有讲过。
怎么去加这些扭扣细节啊。
我这边的话快速的过一下。
首先我选一个圆环。
然后宽度呢。
因为我的洞是10。
宽度可以稍微宽一点12。
然后呢。
加扭扣啊。
我没有直接加在洞里。
因为你在洞里点是加不上扭扣的。
扭扣必须要在板片上加。
所以这里没有办法。
必须要偏移一点。
那你在这加。
一个个加会比较花时间。
所以可以直接在线上右键啊。
快速的来加。
然后扭扣的数量是4个。
这边还不能选。
我做小一点啊。
间距是24个。
因为我刚刚是。
间距是20啊。
这些洞。
然后上面这个设定呢。
距离左边的话是。
这边是20对吧。
那我就20。
然后这个间距是。
距离上面的。
上面的话是20。
是10啊。
是我前面做这个内部。
内部圆的这个距离。
可以稍微再小一点。
只要这个中心也在板片上就可以了。
所以我稍微小一点。
把这个圆做上。
正好说之前有人问金属属性怎么调对吧。
选中你的对象。
比如说你是扭扣就选扭扣。
如果你是织物。
你就选织物啊。
这是一样的。
织物的话。
有这个类型可以选。
然后我这边是扭扣嘛。
选中扭扣。
在属性分析里面找到类型。
里面有一个metal。
是金属的。
这边就变成金属的了。
然后呢。
对这些扭扣可以看到现在位置是偏移的。
所以呢。
选中这些扭扣。
做几个事情。
第一个。
把冲突关掉。
假设你不小心开启模拟了。
然后你又开着冲突。
等一下这个地方就完全就坏掉了。
所以一定要把冲突关掉。
然后呢。
在3D里面啊。
你框选出这些扭扣。
用这个定位球。
正对着这些扭扣。
用定位球去移动。
往里推。
好。
在推动的过程中你可以看到它陷进去了。
所以这时候你可以把扭扣的厚度给它做的再厚一点。
摆到侧面。
往里推。
这样正反面都可以看到扭扣了啊。
然后可以再调整一下位置。
不要看到那个边缘的黑黑的那个部分。
好。
这样子的话一边就完成了。
那另外一边很简单。
Ctrl C Ctrl V。
你可以当然再单击线段输入数据啊。
但这里的话我就直接。
Ctrl C Ctrl V。
然后按着Shift的键在这边单击就行了。
位置不用很准确。
因为我们是不用冲突的。
是直接通过这个定位球来调整它的位置的啊。
然后来到侧面。
把它往里推。
再进来一点。
稍微稍微再出来一点点啊。
不要太多。
好。
那这样的话这个部分就完成了。
你用预设的金属感觉也不太硬。
嗯。
你说的是用的金属面料吗?
不太硬。
硬的话。
就是说植物的物理属性有关哦。
物理属性和它的这个材质是完全两码事了。
如果你要硬一点的话。
你把弯曲强度这个这三个调大。
它就可以变硬了。
材质是材质。
才是它的一个外观表现。
是它的一个光泽度的上面的一个体现啊。
就是它们俩是本质上还是有差异的。
继续啊。
刚刚还有一那个一排抹钉对吧。
在扭扣这边再加一个。
抹钉其实很简单。
我相信这边大部分。
同学应该都知道怎么加。
加扭扣工具。
抹钉小一点。
八毫米。
不要太大啊。
六件。
然后上面距离的话。
你可以做的小一点。
间距的话。
比如说是十五。
二十。
不够。
比如说是三十。
然后呢。
你把这个间距。
下面这个反复是指每一个扭扣之间的一个间距啊。
你可以做的。
小一点。
差不多。
你可以看这边的。
扭扣位置啊。
好像不太合适。
四十二。
差不多。
嗯。
点击OK。
好。
这个扭扣呢。
也选择一个金属材质。
来头。
那你可以看这个扭扣现在是浮在上面的啊。
所以呢。
这些扭扣呢。
它的。
嗯。
选中这些扭扣啊。
要用编辑选择移动扭工具选择它们。
这时候在属性编辑器里面可以设定它线的长度。
当然冲突也要关闭啊。
线的长度给它设定一个复制。
它就可以往回走了。
就可以线下去了啊。
然后呢。
我们把这个。
Ctrl C。
Ctrl V。
按住Shift键。
单击右键。
Shift不放单击右键啊。
距离下端是6毫米。
点击确认。
这样子的话。
上下的扭扣就全部加好了。
整片亮片的效果怎么做。
嗯。
你可以看看上次的那个IV老师的直播。
他有讲到亮片的做法哦。
然后我们继续往下吧。
好。
先把今天的课讲完。
好吧。
嗯。
这是腰带的一个处理啊。
那腰带做完之后呢。
你就可以把它冷冻住了。
选中所有版片。
右键。
群组啊。
这样你下次只要单击就可以了。
Ctrl K。
冷冻。
扭扣怎么全选。
用选择移动扭扣工具。
Ctrl A。
你就可以全选所有的扭扣了。
但是你要看。
这是会把所有不同类型的扭扣都选出来的。
好。
我们再往下。
讲到那个麻绳。
就是最后一个麻绳的制作啊。
麻绳其实这边主要是用一个织物来表现的。
先说说它这个圆的圆绳怎么做。
前面有同学在问。
好。
我现在假设在帽子上去做一个圆绳。
那首先呢。
我要先用编辑版面工具来量一下我这个帽口的长度啊。
当然你可能也要知道你这个帽绳。
就是那个圆绳的厚度是怎样的。
就是它是。
一厘米厚还是多少厚。
那我这边量了一下。
大概是20毫米啊。
所以我用这个四边形版片工具。
先创建一个宽度是20毫米的。
高度的话。
先150吧。
如果你想确定你这个帽绳做多长合适呢。
你可以先把这个版片放过来。
样一样啊。
比如说哎。
觉得短了。
我再长一点。
再长一点。
好。
差不多这么长做这个帽绳。
当然。
但是跟生产挂钩是对绳子是有一个确定的长度的。
你可以根据那个帽绳长。
比如说剪去你这个帽子上的这个长度。
那剩余留出来的是多长。
你就知道了啊。
就是根据你们自己需求去算。
假设这边我其实只需要就是一个效果。
我对尺寸如果说没有什么特别的要求的话。
重置2D。
我就根据这个尺寸来做。
为了做帽绳。
为了做圆绳。
让它圆圆的。
我们知道这个版片非常小。
你要让它圆起来。
粒子间就必须降低啊。
不然它是非常平的。
是做不出那个圆圆的效果的。
那这边粒子间就直接降到1就可以了。
也不用1。
其实到3也够啊。
1或1到3都可以。
根据你自己电脑的情况来啊。
然后呢。
我这边选中两条边。
在线段间创建内部线去做一个中心线。
好。
然后呢。
用这个翻折工具啊。
我把这个版片翻一下。
让它有一个有一个趋势。
然后呢。
就可以用缝纫工具把它两端缝起来了。
好。
给它两端先加个固定针固定一下。
避免它掉下去。
或者你其实加一端也可以。
主要目的是防止它掉下去。
好。
这个内部线可以拿掉了。
再模拟一下。
这个原绳就做出来了。
说一下重点啊。
粒子间距一定要降低。
然后做一条中心线。
翻折一下。
给它一个趋势。
就可以了。
像这个绳子呢。
右上角的定位球。
右上角这个快速安排啊。
你就可以把它放过来。
放在。
比如说放在这个位置。
然后给它往外提一提。
靠近我的帽绳的那个孔啊。
然后呢。
给它缝一下。
缝的时候注意啊。
我是把我的那个。
那个叫什么。
拼合线是藏在靠下的位置。
因为这样的话。
我正面就看不到它了。
因为等一下我如果。
用这个面料的话。
我是可以看到这个接缝的。
等于是不好看。
会有一个。
穿帮的这种感觉啊。
所以要把这根线。
藏在下面。
缝完之后。
检查一下你缝线。
方向对不对啊。
不对的话。
你就把它。
调换一下。
或者旋转一下。
怎样的。
让它这个方向是能够。
直着对上去的。
模拟一下。
就不要让它扭着缝上去。
因为这个板片。
现在力已经就很小。
如果扭的话。
等一下会花很长时间来模拟它。
看得津津有味啊。
那就好。
怎么卷了。
什么意思。
你说这个板片怎么是卷起来。
变圆的吗。
刚才我有做。
几个设定。
这里怎么了。
刚刚反正方向不对啊。
给它调换了一下。
嗯。
卷。
怎么卷的。
我刚刚就是。
在里面加。
在这两个线中间加一个中心内部线。
没关系。
我等一下再做一下。
好吧。
来。
另外一边我再做一下。
比如说。
我Ctrl C。
Ctrl V。
我首先画一个长条的板片。
这个是你可以用这个板片工具去画。
然后之后用编辑板片工具。
刚刚没看到的。
现在看好哦。
选择。
Let's re-set this plate a little bit.
I just talked about adding an internal line.
After adding the internal line, use this folding arrangement tool
to fold this plate a little bit
so that it has a curved trend.
Then use this sewing line to sew them together on both sides.
So it has this trend.
But now it can't be simulated
because the particle diameter of the plate is too large now.
If you want it to roll round and round,
you must reduce the particle diameter.
I've already reduced it to 3 here.
Then press W and add a fixing pin.
Now it can be simulated.
The fixing pin is added to prevent it from falling off.
Then this internal line can now be deleted.
It's already folded.
After deleting it, it becomes round.
Okay.
Then I'll do this rope again.
Use the quick arrangement tool in the upper right corner
to put it over here.
Come over here.
Just get close to this circle.
Get close to this circle.
Okay.
Then sew this to it.
Then this rope,
if you want to adjust it,
you can adjust its length.
It is recommended not to adjust it too much at a time.
A little bit of adjustment.
Because if you adjust it too much,
it is a round tube.
It will deform later.
There will be a hole.
Okay.
This round tube is done.
Next, I will tell you how to show this rope.
This part is actually a process of physical processing.
Here, in order to save time,
I made a video for you.
So here you can watch this video directly.
Let me explain to you.
First of all, I just found a picture of a rope.
I just found it online.
Of course, you can also find a rope and scan it.
Then, in Photoshop, first of all,
I found a picture of a rope.
Then, I found a picture of a rope.
First, I made a transparent cut to it.
For the selected area,
you need to pay attention to the area you choose.
It can be connected up and down.
It is best to be connected up and down.
Our ultimate goal is to make the selected area
into a four-dimensional picture.
So when you choose the area,
pay attention to it.
Try to make it as easy as possible to do it in a four-dimensional manner.
Use this as the basis to choose this area.
Then, next, I made a position in the filter.
Next, I used a cardstock tool
to put this picture together.
You may need to move it many times in this process.
You may have done it from one angle,
but you'll find that there's still a gap
So you have to do a few more moves
until you move it to the back and go,
oh, almost no gap.
Then, save this picture.
Shaded
Shaded, wait a minute, let's see
Let's finish this
And then just now, after making a picture
I found that it is used in
There will be an obvious dark border line in the cloud
So go back
Go back to Photoshop and use that
Uh
That's it
The light adjustment tool is deepening
Simplification, yes, the simplification tool simplifies it
Then at this time
Take a look at the size of the picture you just created
Then in Pixpant
Create a picture according to this size
Put this picture in
Create all 3D pictures
Anyway
You don't have to do anything special
Special settings
Just click OK to create it
After creating
The main thing we need to adjust is
Displacement map
Other pictures are fine, the problem is not big
But we want to show
The texture of this bumpy rope
Mainly through this
Is this Displacement map
Ah
I used this here
His brush tool to put it
The white part is heavier
Make it stand out more
A little more
Then
Save all these 3D pictures
Maybe we
It's not that all the pictures can be used
But just save it step by step
Then you will get so many pictures
Ah
Then we go back to the cloud
Apply this texture to it
Ah
The corresponding texture
Put it on the texture
The hair line map puts it on the hair line map
Displacement map puts it in the position of the displacement map
One by one
You can adjust its size
Because I found this online
So the size of the rope is not 1 to 1
Maybe it should be adjusted a little bit
Ah, because we use the displacement map to show it
So the displacement map must be through
Glossy window
To see the effect of this bumpy
Then you can see it
It's too obvious now
So you can reduce the degree of displacement
Then I put the displacement example in front
From the default 4 to 2
In order to make its surface
Is uh
More simulated
More delicate
You can see that this rope is
One by one
Of course you can also
Remove color and change one color
So everyone sees that 3D
The red rope is actually made like this
Then if you want
Um, change other colors
There is also a method
Because Glossy will make it
Uh, the brightness
The contrast is weak
So you can also choose to do it in Photoshop
Remove color
Adjust its color
Make its white more obvious
Then give it a color layer
Then through this color layer
Uh, the color combination
Uh, in this case, you will see
This texture will be more realistic
Just keep it
At the same time
Changed the color
The metal cross chain of the female bag
Um
Uh
You can try
You can try this
Because its chain
There is a gap in the middle
Uh
You may want to try
Theoretically
Uh
Uh, in this case
You can also see
Through Photoshop processing
The texture
After this color is put on
The reality will be higher
Compared to the effect of direct color removal
Okay, this is like this
So everyone can see
I just made a numbness here
Uh, plant documents
So let's take a look
This numbness
First of all, it has a default
The pattern is an ordinary pattern
Then there is a hair line
Then the most important thing about it
The degree of change
Is when you show it
The feeling of its out
Is strong or weak
Then one to two
In fact, it can be more natural
The larger the particle lens
The more rough it may be
In this case, I am one
Or two
In fact, it can be
If your computer is more
It's more difficult to calculate
You use two
Okay
Then you can get it in the end
Take a look
Here
Not here
In the end, you can get this effect
Then zoom in for everyone
Look
In the end, it looks like this
By the way, this god head
The performance of the god head is actually very simple
In Halloween Dreams
Found one of his
I made it directly with the preset in the library
Use the code and codeants document
Look at the chat
Different colors
Pattern fur
fabric
Different colors
Pattern fur
Use that
Feather in the type of plant
Go to the setting
Then you put your color
Put the pattern in
The pattern is placed
It can be based on your pattern
Color to generate colorful fur
If this is specific
You can go to that
We have a hair dyeing special live broadcast
You are in the master car series
You go to that video
He has a detailed explanation of each hair
What does the setting mean
Well
Is it the same size of the pattern and pattern?
Yes
If you are not only the pattern and pattern
You can see all the pattern
Hair line
Including if you have this highlight
The size of these pictures must be the same
Otherwise
This effect will be wrong
Will be wrong
So you finally have to keep it
In the conversion
The size of each picture is the same
So here
If you want to adjust the size of the pattern
All the pictures are added
Then adjust
In this way
It will automatically adjust its size at the same time
I put that
The head is not finished
This is a head
The head is in the warehouse
For example, I use one
Increase to the working area
Just add it
No need to add model size
And then this rope
I don't need it
It's a board
We can see it here
Delete it
These two heads
Will be retained
3D form
OBJ Trim
It is in the form of a secondary
How is it generated
We are in the file
Just
There is an open or add
There is one called accessories
Its beginning is
Insert OBJ
Then when you enter OBJ
Choose to enter as Trim
Then this
Maybe first you have to have a
3D OBJ model file
Where to come from
Maybe you need to use other 3D software
For example, 3D Max or Maya
To create
If you don't have resources or technology
Then use Cloud
Then I delete one
Choose one directly
Click
Then click your rope
In this way
This small solid component
Will stick to this rope
At this time
I'll give it a little more
Click again
You can turn it off
Then put it over
Still a little big
It's done
Then you can turn it into one
Plastic is plastic
Use a red color
That's it
Move a little more
Ctrl C
Ctrl V
Copy to the other side
Just adjust the position
That's it
Then it's done
The advantage of pinching accessories
When you simulate
This accessory can follow your rope
And it has weight
Can make you this rope
Looks more realistic
In this way
The whole style is done
Which one is pressed
Single click on your copy
There are two icons in the upper right corner of the locator
This is the left one
Single click
You see your locator shape has changed
It's done
Click again
This icon will turn off the release function
Four-box
Four-box can be done
In the lock
For example, add one
Clo's preset lock
There is a pair of four-box
You choose
This pair
Then add one
The second one
You choose another one
Then you just have a pair
Then you should
What position should the corresponding lock be added to
Finally, pay attention to your
All these locks are the same as before
Do an operation
Put your lock
The conflict is closed for him
Don't let the locks fight each other
Then there is another setting
Because you are a four-box
You can't use these two locks to merge him
Because there are only lock and lock eyes in the lock
Then you can use a false pin
Is the false pin that I just mentioned
Go to your corresponding
Just set the position for him
How did the lock go to one side
Maybe he was just operating
The lock has returned to the initial position
It doesn't matter
Just move it back
It's a little inconvenient here
Because the position of our lock is biased
So sometimes he
In the process of processing
If you accidentally let the lock reset the position
He will have such a problem
You go to a group of units
Just adjust it for him
The original god turned out to be a dark brown
How did it turn white
Original god
You choose this rope
Then click on the color in the text
It turns white
That's it
It becomes a white rope
How to reduce the weight of the key
Click on the key
You can find its weight in the attribute editor
Here
There is a weight below the specifications
Go here
Thank you
Make a flat rope inside
Let's talk about the four folds
Find this rope
What about this rope
You have to make it thick through this rendering thickness
This is the flat rope
If you want to be a little bit rounder
Make this width narrower
Make the thickness thicker
Just let it slowly become like this
So in fact, a single version can also be made into a round rope
It's just that the texture of the round rope may not be able to continue so well
You can see that the texture here cannot be continued
Teacher, I don't know when I'll go home today
I'll finish your questions as soon as I finish answering them
The details you mentioned just now
The details
Okay
Then I'll save it for a while
Save it for a while
Because the example of this clothing is very small
There are too many details and the speed is too slow
So open one again
The details are too small
If you have a short waist
Can I go with the rope?
Can go together
But the part of the knot just now
That's the waist line
There are too many details
The version is very small
Not suitable for walking show
If you want to walk show
I suggest you
I suggest you put that just now
The part of the belt
That's the part of the belt
That's the one below
Um...
Maybe you need to put the waist
The part of the waistline
Don't let it really be a patterned form
For simulation
That part
Tsk
It may be more dangerous
If you want to walk on the show
Don't wear it in this way
Because just to talk about the details of B-strips
It's the way to wear the real waistline
One move, one move
If you want to walk on the show
You do it in the way of sewing
This...
The details of the dress
What does it mean
Let me open a picture to explain
This is
You sew the plate from here
Sew it here
Sew it from here to here
End
Just follow the sewing method
Make a fake one
To walk on the show
If it's like this
It's basically impossible to walk on the show
What about the next butterfly?
You can
Um...
Or use a copy
Otherwise, you put your bag
Use a fake one
Set it up with you
Otherwise, it will float too much
It will be unstable
Talk about the details
I'll just do it like this
Anyway, the details
Big and small
It's basically a very short line
With a very long line
Or set the elasticity
Ah, no matter which way
There will always be a fabric pile
Then when this happens
The first thing to pay attention to is to reduce the particle diameter
Reduce the contact thickness to one
This is the most basic
Second, you have to see the obvious details
If you break it
Pay attention
Suppose you're on fire
Ah, I'm not serious
Here
Suppose you're on fire
In the state of life
If you do a simulation
Is what we normally do
The clothes may be a short line
And a long line
Sewn together
Ah, we need to pay attention
Set up a flexibility for your short line
Otherwise you see
This place is now
It's been stretched
So you have to set a 100% flexibility for the short line
You can increase the strength appropriately
When you keep this line
Maintain its length
Then, if your fold is not obvious, check your plant's physical properties.
Usually, Cloud's default plant, for example, the old version of the default plant,
its fold is not much, because its bending strength is relatively large.
Including the current 5.2 version of the default plant will be much better.
Its bending strength has become smaller, so the fold will be a little more.
And sometimes, for example, you use a snow-covered fabric,
for example, it is a snow-covered fabric with the best line strength as 0.
It is difficult to make wrinkles.
And sometimes, for example, it is easy to deform.
There are some, what else?
Maybe this one will be a little more.
This is called snow-covered.
Of course, it is not obvious.
Maybe my fabric is very...
The amount of fabric is very large.
It will be a little more obvious.
If your fabric is not much fold, then the fold is not a very obvious situation.
Pay attention to check your plant's physical properties.
If one of them is deformed, is it 0?
If it is 90, it may not have wrinkles.
If it is 90, adjust it to 0.
If the line strength of the corner is 0, you can consider adjusting it appropriately.
Because sometimes the line strength of the corner is 0, its wrinkles do not appear easily.
Of course, if you are just a small part, you will let that small part adjust the fabric separately.
This is a point.
And for example, if you are in this state, it still does not have very fine wrinkles.
Then use a function called draw.
Click on this line.
In the attribute editor, click on this.
Find the draw and open it.
Because now the particle diameter is 5.
It hasn't broken yet.
Because the particle diameter is not enough.
So continue to draw it.
Just add the draw function.
In this way, you can see that this part is shown with a more delicate particle diameter.
You can see that there is a gap in the setting below the draw.
The particle diameter has reached 1 mm.
This is a more delicate fold.
If it's not enough.
You can consider adding it.
Add a thinning.
Add an internal rectangle here.
Then add a thinning to it.
Of course, this method has a closed end.
It may have a little trace.
For example, the thinning ratio is 20.
In this way, the surface of this area will be thinner.
It will produce more fine wrinkles.
This will come according to your actual needs.
Closet tutorial.
Closet.
You can take a look at that for the time being.
Closet official.
It has a tutorial.
If you are one of our business clients.
You can contact our responsible teacher separately.
Then we have something to explain to business clients.
It's really a big release tonight.
So everything that came today is worth it.
Add a row of certain operations.
You can see it clearly.
It's okay.
You wait for the next broadcast.
Just wait for the broadcast to come out.
How to adjust the size of the material shrink chart.
I don't really understand this question.
It's almost here today.
If you have any questions.
Personal customer.
Personal customers, you go to our official website.
There is that discussion area.
Is on our forum.
You ask.
There will be a professional answer.
That's all for today.
And if you have any questions today.
If you haven't replied yet.
If we get a reply, we'll look at it later.
And then I didn't reply to it.
I'll tell you when the next live broadcast starts.
That's what we always have a pre-reviewing session.
And then I'll give you a preview of the next live broadcast.
You can take a look.
Next time is October 30th.
And then the theme is to make a sachet.
It's also the style that everyone was shouting about and wanted to learn.
How do you do it?
You can take a look at the previous basic teaching video.
It seems to have
The way of making a sachet and the previous basic tutorial.
There's a smark dress in it.
That's about the same.
You can take a look at the basic tutorial.
A live broadcast that specializes in calligraphy and calligraphy.
We had a live broadcast with Mr. Lydia before.
It's about the text processing.
You can take a look at the playback.
Okay, okay, okay.
Thank you all for today.
That's all for our live broadcast.
See you next time.